MENEN SZYMON

Junior developper

If you are looking for someone who is curious and highly motivated, I am the right person for you.

Available: April 2023

Contacts:

szymonmenenwork@gmail.com

Menen Szymon in

Simone Menou



Target position:

Web-application developer: Front-end, Back-end, Full-stack

Technical skills

Back-end











Front-end •









Development tools

























Project management ● ● ●





Soft skills

- · Sense of responsibility
- Organization
- Teamwork
- Autonomous
- Curiosity
- Creativity

Motivation

After several years in various sectors, I have finally found a job in which I think I can fully develop. To do so, I have followed several training courses. In order to concretize this, I wish to apply the skills and technical knowledge I have at my disposal to a company in order to start my professional reconversion.

22 23 24 25

Goal

Following the training within interface 3 I am looking for an internship as a junior backend developer, full-stack or front-end for a period of 2 months apd from April 17, 2023.

LINGUISTIC COMPETENCIES

French

English Dutch



"My multiple experiences in diverse and varied sectors have allowed me to acquire a versatile profile."



Professional experience

PRODUCTION ASSISTANT

Festival des Blocs

Edition 2018,2019,2020

- Organization and management of logistics before and during the event (rental/purchase of filming equipment, quotes etc.).
- Follow up on planning, drafting of contracts for technicians and contributors
- Assist the production management in all its activities.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

La maison des parents Solo 2020:

· Layout of the activity report

Asbl Solidarité savoir 2018:

 Redesign of the graphic charter: brochure, prints, posters

TEAM MANAGER

Le 5éme élément /2010 - 2019 Restauant Little Tokyo / 2016 - 2017 Restauant La fabbrica (Tour &Taxi | 2015 - 2016 Catering and cultural places Via Via /Micro market | 2014/2015

WAITRESS/BARMAID

Restaurant AMI | 2018 Fernand Obb | 2019 Brewdog brewery | 2016 - 2017 Brasserie Verschuren /2008 - 2009 PP café /2006 - 2009

EXTRAS

Saisons | 2010 - 2019

 Seasonal work in Knokke for selling ice cream and waffles. Autonomous work consisting in managing the shed from opening to closing, maintaining the work space, ensuring the service, managing the daily stock.

youplaboum ASBL| 2010 - 2016

· Facilitator in a creativity education center

Education

CECAF (15mois) -2022/2023

Web-application / full-stack developper : Interface 3 Bruxelles

Qualification in Computer Graphics (2ans) - 2010

Evening classes at the Saint Luc Institute Brussels

. C.E.S.I Plastic art 2006

Saint Luc Institute Brussels

Pre-training

Prêt-à coder (3month) October 2021

- HTML/CSS
- Python
- MySQL
- PHP

ADN technologie (2 weeks) jully 2021

- Introduction to Javascript
- · Advanced Wordpress

Milocs (2month) Mai 2021

- HTML/CSS
- Ruby
- Web-oriented English
- Arithmetic logic course
- (Flogorythm)

Molengeek: Webmaster school june 2020

• wordpress beginner

E-learning Sololearn:

- HTML/HTML5
- CSS/CSS3
- javascript
- PHP
- Ruby

Open classrooms:

- HTML/CSS
- PHP